---------------------------------------------------------------------------------
  Changelog for "Rainbeau's Etched Stone Walls"
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------

- 12/05/2018
	- Removed patch previously required for smoothing NPS's basalt.
	- Rewrote XML patches to improve load efficiency slightly.

- 11/04/2018
	- Added fixes to allow basalt from "Nature's Pretty Sweet" to be smoothed and
	  etched.
	  
- 10/29/2018
	- Inside corners will no longer be "auto-smoothed," as while that feature is
	  fine in vanilla, where smoothed walls come in one and only one flavor, it
	  doesn't work so well in the context of the mod.
	- Pawns can now smooth and/or etch inside corners themselves.
	
- 10/23/2018
	- An additional quick code fix to prevent short hash conflicts.
	
- 10/23/2018
	- Changed the mod's name from "Smooth Stone Walls" to "Etched Stone Walls."
	- Replaced the code that puts etching icons on the task bar. This should get
	  rid of the huge performance hits some players were seeing when selecting
	  multiple items.
	  
- 10/22/2018
	- Updated to RimWorld 1.0 release! (b19 was skipped.)
	- Removed basic smoothing functionality from the mod, since that's now a
	  vanilla capability. The mod now just allows etching and decorating.
	- Rewrote much of the code to accommodate vanilla's smoothing system, which
	  is rather different than the system used in earlier versions of this mod.
	- Added etching and decorating to task bar when smoothed wall tiles are
	  selected, so it's now possible to pick a wall segment and designate it to
	  be etched, instead of having to select "etch" from the architect menu and
	  then pick a wall segment or segments.
	- Updated the version of the Harmony library the mod uses.
	- Removed "Mod Sync Ninja" files.

- 01/01/2018
	- Squashed the bug I inadvertently introduced that messed up display of 
	  decorated walls.

- 01/01/2018
	- The mod is now compatible with the altered stone and wall graphics used in
	  "Cupro's Stones."
	- Skill gain rates for smoothing (construction) and basic etching (crafting) 
	  have been cut in half. The skill gain rate for decorating (artistic) has
	  not been changed.

- 12/04/2017
	- It is now possible to smooth basalt rock walls from the "Nature's Pretty
	  Sweet" mod.
	- The mod now also works with the "Mod Sync Ninja" updater.

- 12/03/2017
	- Conduits no longer prevent etching or decorating of walls.
	- The priority of wall smoothing has been dropped a bit so that it's above
	  deconstruction but below other actual construction tasks.

- 11/13/2017
	- Added Russian language translation files provided by kr33man.

- 11/12/2017
	- Added Japanese language translation files by Proxyer.

- 11/12/2017
	- Updated to RimWorld b18 release.
	- Basic etching is now a crafting job rather than a construction job, giving
	  crafting rather than construction XP.
	- Decorative etching is still an art job, but no longer provides construction
	  XP, instead giving only artistic XP, as it should.
	- The priority of the basic "smooth wall" job has been raised so that it's
	  comparable to other basic construction jobs, so that pawns are more
	  likely to actually smooth walls, even with other jobs in the queue.

- 07/30/2017
	- Coolers and vents can now be placed directly on smoothed walls just as on
	  vanilla walls.

- 06/08/2017
	- Replaced XML overwrites with patches for better compatibility with other
	  mods.
	- Added new embrasure textures consistent with the revised wall graphics,
	  which should automatically be used if another mod in use adds embrasures.

- 06/06/2017
	- XML defs no longer try to inherit from core abstracts. (Not only is this 
	  change a good idea, anyway, but it also fixed the "Map Reroll" issue.)

- 06/04/2017
	- Pawns are once again able to smooth the inside corners of mountain rooms!
	  "And there was much rejoicing."
	- Reduced the time it takes to smooth a wall to about 3/4 of what it was
	  before. This should represent a bit of a savings over the time required to
	  mine a tile and then build a new wall, without making smoothing too
	  overpowered.
	- Made a change to the XML wall defs which I'd hoped would fix the "Map
	  Reroll" wall graphics glitch. It didn't actually fix the glitch, but it's
	  probably a good change, anyway.
	- Added "[RF]" prefix tag to the mod's name for easier mod list sorting.

- 05/27/2017
	- Fixed German language file, which I'd inadvertently corrupted.

- 05/26/2017
	- New German translation file added, courtesy of Steam user Lauri7x3.
	- It should no longer be possible for traders to show up with etched walls in
	  their inventories.

- 05/09/2017
	- Potential roof collapse while smoothing or etching walls should no longer
	  be an issue.

- 05/07/2017
	- Updated to RimWorld alpha 17.
	- Added the ability to "undecorate" walls.
	- Pawns now gain artistic skill when they complete decorative etchings.
	- Removed the out of date and incomplete German translation file.

- 04/23/2017
	- The mod now uses the Harmony library instead of detouring core methods.
	  
- 04/22/2017
	- It is now possible to do either basic or decorative etching. Decorative
	  etching can be done by any pawn assigned to artistic work, and results in
	  some wall tiles being randomly adorned with pictures in addition to the
	  brick pattern. (Pawns with higher artistic skill are more likely to
	  actually produce such art.)

- 04/19/2017
	- Added the ability to "etch" smoothed stone walls to give them the same
	  brick pattern that constructed walls have, if you prefer that all of your
	  wall tiles look the same.
	- You should now be able to smooth any type of natural stone wall, added by
	  any mod, rather than just those added by specific mods I happen to be aware
	  of.

- 04/11/2017
	- Improved both the constructed and the smoothed wall graphics so they "flow"
	  well graphically not only into each other, but also into natural rock
	  walls.

- 04/10/2017
	- Filled some "gaps" in the smoothed stone wall definition, which will
	  perhaps fix some odd errors that some users have seen.
	- Fixed the greyscaling on the smooth stone wall graphics to better match the
	  greyscaling on the block stone wall graphics, so stone walls will "flow"
	  better graphically from constructed to smoothed segments.

- 04/09/2017
	- Smoothed walls are now a distinct wall type, slightly more durable than
	  stone walls constructed with blocks. When deconstructed, smooth stone walls
	  don't yield blocks, but have the same chance as mined stone tiles to drop
	  stone chunks.
	- Squashed a bug which yielded "free" granite walls when a tile was set to be
	  both mined and smoothed.

- 03/10/2017
	- Non-vanilla wall compatibility no longer requires separate dll files.

- 03/05/2017
	- Allowed for compatibility with non-vanilla walls from the "Minerals and
	  Materials" and "Kura's Extra Minerals" mods.
	- Smoothing stone walls now requires Stonecutting research, to prevent free
	  access to bricks in tribal start games.
	- Smoothed walls now automatically belong to your faction and don't need to
	  be claimed.

- 02/26/2017
	- German translation file added, courtesy of Steam user Axel.

- 02/25/2017
	- Initial release.
